Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers
Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
5B
Bullock, Robert "Bob" Douglas, Sr., 1929 - 1999
337 document boxes
The Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts collection documents Bullock’s service in the Office of Comptroller of Public Accounts in Texas from 1975-1990. The collection contains correspondence, notebooks, itineraries, publications, reports, and various files.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
In 1969, Bullock joined the staff of incoming Governor Preston Smith and served as appointments secretary and general counsel before Governor Smith named him Secretary of State in 1971. Bullock's service as Texas Secretary of State was marked by major election law reforms, including Bullock's implementation of the first state-financed party primaries and an extensive broadening of campaign finance disclosure requirements.
Bullock left state service at the end of 1972 and again set up an Austin law practice. By the end of 1973, he was well on his way to his first statewide race for State Comptroller.
He served as Comptroller for the next 16 years, turning the office into a model agency with a special emphasis on financial research and taxpayer service.
Bullock recognized early in his career the value of the press. When he became Comptroller in 1975, an important part of his administration was to begin diligent collection of state sales taxes. He discovered too many businesses collected state sales taxes from their customers but failed to report and remit those taxes to the state. As part of a “voluntary compliance” campaign, Bullock would invite the press to Comptroller visits to businesses owing significant amounts of state sales taxes. Armed with estimates of past due taxes, Bullock and Comptroller enforcement officers would arrive unannounced at a business and ask for payment of back taxes. If the business owners did not pay, enforcement officers would seize inventory and cash registers. These raids on delinquent businesses spawned cartoons, editorials, and invaluable press coverage, including some suggestions that Bullock was grandstanding. But the statewide press coverage of “Bullock’s Raiders” made important and valuable impressions on delinquent taxpayers and on the average tax paying Texan.
Bullock’s service as Comptroller ended in 1990 when he was elected to the office of Lieutenant Governor.
Scope and Content
From 1975 to 1990, Bullock’s political career encompassed 16 years of public service as Texas Comptroller of Public Accounts. The Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts collection is divided into seven series: Correspondence, Issues, Itineraries, Notebooks, Policies and Procedures, Reports, and Publications.
The sheer transformation and growth of the Comptroller’s office is evident in the physical record of this series and is its strength. Bullock completely reformed the Comptroller’s Office, and every subseries in this series reflects that in some manner. The issue files, notebooks, policies and procedures, and reports subseries contain the most visible evidence of the transformation and growth Bullock accomplished in his 16 years as Texas’ Comptroller of Public Accounts.
Arrangement
Consists of seven subseries: Correspondence, Issue Files, Itineraries, Notebooks, Policies and Procedures, Reports, and Publications.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 5B. Acquired 1998-03-15
Related Resources
Related references
Ball, Benna, and Ben Rogers. A Guide to the Bob Bullock Collection. Waco, TX: Baylor Office of Public Relations, 2004.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Bullock, Bob -- Archives.; Bullock, Bob -- Travel.
Subjects (Organizations)
Texas. Comptroller's Office -- Records and correspondence.; Texas. Comptroller's Office.
Places
Texas -- Economic conditions -- Sources.
Subjects
Apportionment (Election law) -- Texas.; Controllership -- Texas.; Public schools -- Texas.; Sales tax -- Texas.
Genres
Business correspondence.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Legislative materials.; Maps.; Notebooks.
- Correspondence, 1975-1990; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Correspondence section of this series is arranged into general correspondence, media correspondence (alpha and mass form mailings), and staff correspondence. Staff correspondence is restricted, please contact archivist for further information. Other portions may also be restricted. The series is in good condition.
  - General, 1975-1990; 1
    - 1975-1986, 1
      - Abio, Julian, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Aboussie, T.A., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Abrams, J.D., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Acers, Maurice, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Ackerman, Freda Stern, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Adair, Kelly, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Adami, Ray, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Adams, Donald G., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Adams, Herman, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Adams, Colonel James B., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Adams, Jean P. & Frankie, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Abbott, Carol, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Abel, Malcolm D., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Abercrombie, John B. & V.T., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Abernethy, Francis Edwin, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Abington, James W., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Abington, William “Bill”, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Adams, John G., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Adams, Linda, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Adamson, Dan K., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Adkins, Jean, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Adkisson, Hon. Thomas F., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Adrian, Curtis B., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Agather, Ruth, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Agnich, Fred J., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Aguirre, Robert B., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Aikin, Hon. A.M. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Aiken, Hon. Ed Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Akers, Fred, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Alaniz, Nago L., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Alba, R. Jerry A., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Albert, H.A., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Alberts, Larry C., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Albertson, Weldon C., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Alcorn, Allen, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Alcorn, Charles W., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Albright, William L., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Alderman, William B., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Aleshire, Hon. William “Bill”, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Alexander. Lt. Colonel Charles B., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Alexander, Chester & Margaret, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Alexander, Don C., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Alexander, Jack, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Alexander, James, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Alexander, Jerry, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Alexander, Thomas P., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Alford, Fred F. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Alder, B. Michael, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - Alfrey, Mrs. Nefill, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - Allaway, William “Bill” Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Allee, Hon. Henry E., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Allen, Cindy, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Allen, Herbert, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Allen, Hon. Joe, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Allen, R.B., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Allison, Hon. Arthur P., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Allred, Reverend Clifford, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Allred, Mrs. Mell (Beulah), 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Alvarez, Hon. Adolfo, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Alwin, Lawrence F., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Ambrus, Richard A., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Ament, Louise C., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Ames, Brantly, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Amoco Oil Company, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Anderson, Ada, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Anderson, Andy, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Anderson, Barbara, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Anderson, Gary W., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Anderson, James V., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Anderson, Judy, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Anderson, Hon. Louis H., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Anderson, Lynn F., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - M.D. Anderson Hospital & Tumor Institute, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Anderson, M.J. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Anderson, Marilyn, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Anderson, Thomas C., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Anderson, Vicki, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Anderson, Wade, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Andrews, Lowell L., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Andrews, Hon. Michael A., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Andrews, W. Alan, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Andujar, Hon. Betty, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Anglin, Mike, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Ansley, Angelo Napoleon, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Apodaca, Raymond D., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Appleman, Hon. John S., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Aresty, Maurice J., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Armbrister, Hon. Kenneth L., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Armer, Gary, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Armey, Hon. Richard “Dick”, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Armstrong, Sgt. Jack, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Armstrong, Hon. Robert L. “Bob”, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Armstrong, Deane, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Arnois, Herbert P., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Arnold, Ann, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Arnold, Claude, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Arnold, Hon. Gordon D. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Arnold, Jim, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Arnold, Randy, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Arnold, W. Buck, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Arnold, W. Tom, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Arrell, Vernon M., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Arriola, Hon. Ronald S., 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - Arriola, Sylvia, 1975-1986 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - Ash, Dr. Weldon L. & Jan, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Ashbaugh, Edward R. “Ed”, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Ashby, Lynn, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Ashby, Morris E., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Ashley, Bobby, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Ashworth, Kenneth H., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Ashworth, Mary E., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Atkins, James, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Atkinson, Charles, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Atkinson, Hon. Hamp, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Atlas, Hon. Morris, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Attal, Gene, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Atwell, Ben, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Atwell, Robert L. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Austin, O. David, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Autry, Gene, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Auvenshine, Dr. Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Avery, George P., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Avila, Genovena R., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Awalt, W. L., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Ayala, Helen, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Ayers, Hon. Ben P., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Babb, Charles M., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Babbitt, Bruce, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Bacon, Margaret, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Badger, Marguerite, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Bailey, Archie L., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Bailey, Doyne, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Bailey, Joe W., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Bailey, Mary Love, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Bailey, Mrs. O.B., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Bain, Robert B. “Bob”, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Blair, Gerald D., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Bair, Warren C., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Baird, Jonathan C., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Baisdon, Benjamin H., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Baker, Billy B., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Baker, Bud, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Baker, Colbert L. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Baker, Gilbert, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Baker, Junior F., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Baker, Robert E., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Balch, Clarence W., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Baldwin, Robert B., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Bales, Hon. Larry, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Ballard, Glenn A., 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Ballard, Rebecca, 1975-1986 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Banks, W.W., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Bankston, William O., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Bannack, Buck, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Barclay, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Barefield, Charlie, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Barefield, Edgar V., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Barenkamp, Paul, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Barho, Carl, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Barkley, Douglas F., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Barler, Bette B., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Barnes, Hon. Ben, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Barnes, C.F. “Buddy”, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Barnes, Caladonia J., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Barnes, Cindy Kelly, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Barnes, Dee, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Barnes, Jimmy, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Barnes, Hon. Robert N., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Barnett, Billy Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Barnett, Herman, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Barnhart, Hon. Herb, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Barnhart, Hon. Ray, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Barnhill, Hon. John R., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Barnstone, Gertrude, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Baromeo, Chase, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Barrett, Olga, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Barrick, Bruce, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Barrientos, Hon. Gonzalo, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Barringer, Robert W., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Barron, Benjamin K., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Barron, Frank, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Barron, Hon. John M., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Barron, Thomas C., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Barrow, Judge Charles W., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Barta, Carolyn, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Bartlett, Hon. Thomas, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Barton, Hon. Erwin W., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Barton, Jane, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Barton, Richard Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Barton, Hon. Bob Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Barton, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Bartos, Jerry, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Bartula, Paul F., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Basham, Fred T., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Bass, R. Byrnie Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Bass, Perry R., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Bass, Hon. Robert W. “Bob”, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Batis, Pat, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Batson, Joseph E., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Batson, Rose, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Battersby, Jim A. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Bauer, W. H. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Bauerle, Dr. James E., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Bauers, Betty, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Baxter, Elizabeth T., 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Baylor, Don, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Baylor University-School of Law, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Bazan, Raymond A. III “Ray”, 1975-1986 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Beall, Richard L., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Bean, Teresa, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Bean, Hon. Woodrow Wilson, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Beard, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Beard, E.D. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Beard, Pat, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Beard, Tom, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Bearden, Wilton & Nell, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Beasley, Kent, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Beatty, William D., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Beauchamp, D., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Beckham, Heather, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Beckham, J.L., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Beckum, Jay, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Beckworth, L. Gary. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Beckworth, Hon. Lindley, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Bednarek, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Belew, David O. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Belew, John S., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Bell, Carlton, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Belt, K. David, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Benak, Frank, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Benedict, Hon. Jerry L., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Bennett, Herman A., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Bentsen, Hon. Lloyd M. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Beran, Wayne B., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Berger, Donald M., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Bergeron, Fred P., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Bergfeld, Robert N., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Berkebile, Phillip A., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Berlanga, Hon. Hugo, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Berlin, Edgar, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Bernaldez, Eduardo, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Bernstein, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Berrier, E.J., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Berry, Rev. Bishop, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Berry, James D., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Berry, Varreece, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Bertani, C.L. “Chuck”, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Bethke, Monroe, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Beto, George J., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Bezdek, James, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Bibb, Barry, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Bibby, Clarence, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Biesel, Jerry W., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Biggs, Glenn, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Bigham, John R., 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Bingren, Chen, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Bippert, Clinton R., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Bird, Donald E., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Bird, Hon. Ron, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Birdlebough, William E., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Birdwell, Joe A., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Birmingham, Charles, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Bishop, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Bishop, Charles E., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Bishop, Eliza, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Bishop, Jim, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Bivins, James, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Black, Hon. H.D. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Black, John R. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Black, Hon. William B., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Blackburn, Stanley T., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Blackerby, Phillip S., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Blagg, Mary Evelyn, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Blair, Hon. Fred, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Blair, Hon. John, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Blair, Sandy, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Blake, Hon. Roy, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Blakeman, Robert E., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Blakemore, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Blakley, William A., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Blanchard, Robert O., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Blankenship, Hon. Cooper, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Blanton, Jack S. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Blanton, Patricia, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Blanton, Hon. William W., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Bleckley, J.B., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Block, Captain Hyman R. “Lefty”, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Blocker, John R., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Blodgett, Terrell, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Blomquist, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Blomquist, Harry L. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Bloodworth, W.O. “Ty”, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Bloom, Mr. & Mrs. Robert H., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Bloomquist, Eddie, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Blount, Hon. Harry F., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Blount, Robert W. “Pappy”, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Bludworth, W. Milton, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Blythe, Hon. Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Board, Richard, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - Boatner, Yandell Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - Boatwright, Dr. John, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - Bock, Hon. Bennie II, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Bock, Sue, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Bode, James A. “Jim”, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Bode, Hon. Mary Jane, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Bode, Winston, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Boggs, Paul E., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Bohanan, F. Phinks, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Bohlin, Sue, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Bohner, Jay, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Boles, Jo Laynne, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Boldrick, Neill Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Bolles, Ortez & Oleta, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Bolton, Christopher, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Bolton, Claud H. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Bomar, Rev. Fred, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Bomer, Hon. Elton, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Bond, George D., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Bonds, Andy, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Bonilla, Tony, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Bonner, Cathy, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Bonner, George “Poochie”, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Bonner, R.R., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Boone, J.M., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Boothman, Claud O., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Bordie, Camilla, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Boren, LaMoyne Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Bosquez, Mario L., 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)